Guide to the Catalogue Department, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1919-2014; 1990-2014; Accession 2016-A-077
  - Administrative files
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1991-1992 I (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1991-1992 II (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1997-1998 I (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1997-1998 II (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Slavic and East European Division Annual Report 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Specialty Cataloging Annual Report 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Specialty Cataloging Annual Report 2009-2010 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Specialty Cataloging Annual Report 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Specialty Cataloging Annual Report 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Specialty Cataloging Annual Report 2012-2013 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Serial Department Annual Reports from 1919/1920-1935/1936, 1919-1936 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Serial Department Annual Reports from 1936/1937-1940/1941, 1936-1941 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Serial Department Annual Reports from 1941/1942-1945/1946, 1941-1946 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collectors Annual Reports 1965/1966 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collectors Annual Reports: Pt.1 1967/1968 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collectors Annual Reports: Pt.2 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collectors Annual Reports: Pt.1 1968/1969 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collectors Annual Reports: Pt.2 1968/1969 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Yale University Library - Technical Services Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Yale University Library - Catalog Department Annual Report, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports: Pt. 1, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports: Pt. 2, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports: Pt. 3, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Yale University Catalog Department Annual Report: Pt.1, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Yale University Catalog Department Annual Report: Pt.2, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports I 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports I 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports II 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports I 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports II 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - YUL Catalog Dept Annual Report 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Technical Services Catalogue Department Annual Reports 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - YUL Catalog Dept Annual Report 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - YUL Technical Services Annual Report of Associate University Librarian 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - YUL Catalog Dept Annual Report 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - YUL Catalog Dept Annual Report 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - YUL Catalog Dept Annual Report 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - YUL Catalog Dept Annual Report 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Catalog Metadata Services Annual Report 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - YUL Catalog Dept Annual Report 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - YUL Catalog Dept Annual Report 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - YUL Technical Services Annual Report 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Technical Services and Area Studies Collections Annual Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Yale University Library Catalog Department Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Yale University Library Catalog Department Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report, 2010-2011 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report, 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Catalog Department Annual Report, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Cataloger's Desktop Subscription, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Catalog Metadata Services: Finding Aids Database, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Catalog Metadata Services: Finding Aids Database Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Catalog Metadata Services: Reengineering, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Program for Cooperative Cataloging/ Cataloging Now 2, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Program for Cooperative Cataloging/ Cataloging Now, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Collections Security: Final Report to the University Librarian, Parts I and II, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Catalog Use Assessment, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Catalog Department Task Forces, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Cataloging Studies and Research, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Council on Library Resources, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Cooperative Cataloging Council, 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Collection Development Council: Digital Collections Task Force, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Collection Development Council: Media Task Force, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Digital Landscapes: Cyberinfrastructure Survey Summaries Notes, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Digital Landscapes: Meetings, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Digital Landscapes: Focus Groups, 2004-2007 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Digital Landscapes: Miscellaneous Documents, 2005-2007 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Donohue Group Information, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Donohue Group Contract, 2010-2011 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Exchange Programs, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Exchange Orbis Records, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Finding Aids Report, 2004-2007 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Film Study, 2008-2013 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Fortunoff Holocaust Testimonies Preservation Requirements Report, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Gifts Workflow, 2000-2010 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Gay Lesbian Bisexual Transgender Queer Task Force: Meeting Documents, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Goal Setting, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Joint Departmental Committee FY07, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Joint Departmental Committee Cataloging Training, 2003-2008 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Library Transformation: Proposal Drafts, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Library Transformation: Library Transformation Committee, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Library of Congress, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Library Planning, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Joint Steering Committee Conference, 35704 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Library Shelving Facility, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Luna Imaging (Insight): Beinecke Contract Documents, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Library Shelving Facility: Expansion, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Library Shelving Facility: Documents, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Online Computer Library Center Reclamation, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Joint Departmental Committee [JDC]: Training, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - JDC: Best Practices I, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - JDC: Best Practices II, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - JDC - November 2010 Minutes (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Institute of Museum and Library Services [IMLS] Grant: Miscellaneous, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - IMLS: Architecture Grant documents, 2000-2004 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - IMLS: McClintock Grant Application, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - IMLS: Digital McClintock Comments, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - IMLS: McClintock Documents, 1979-2005 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - IMLS: Grant Proposal 2008 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Information Technology Services/Library Services Group AMT/Library Tape Upgrade/Replacement, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - IMLS: National Leadership Grant 2008 Topic Model - Confidential, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - High Performing Organizations Profile [HPO] Survey: 2005 Survey Data (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - HPO Survey: 2005 Survey Analysis (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - HPO Survey: Library Management Council [LMC] Goals, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Hathi Trust Hold, 2012-2014 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Intellectual Property: Copyright/Public Domain/Fair Use…, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - International Programs: Notes and Comments, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Information Technology Services [ITS]: AMT - Statlab, 1996-2005 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Human Relations Area Files [HRAF]: Culture Convservancy, 2000-2005 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Integrated Digital Image Resources [IDIR] Faculty Advisory Committee [FAC] Meeting 7 May 2007 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - IDIR FAC Meeting 12 February 2008 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - IDIR FAC Meeting 7 December 2006 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - IDIR FAC Meeting Scheduling 2006 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - IDIR FAC Meeting 9 May 2006 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - IDIR Quality Control, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - IDIR Planning, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - IDIR FAC Meeting 12 February 2008 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - IDIR: Miscellaneous, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - IDIR: Mid-term Report, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Integrated Access Council [IAC]: Miscellaneous, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - IAC Minutes, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - IAC: Digital Production and Integration Program, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - IAC: Open Archives Initiative - Protocol for Metadata Harvesting, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - IAC: Fedora, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - IAC: Open Archive Initiatives, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - IAC: Digital Preservation Committee, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - IAC: PREMIS, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Endeavor/Voyager: Permanent Agreement for Computer Software, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Endeavor/Voyager: Endeavor Contract, 2001-2004 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Endeavor/Voyager: Contract Related Documents, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Endeavor/Voyager: Ivies + Voyager Meeting (January 2005) (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Endeavor/Voyager: Ivies + Unicode Meeting (December2005) (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - JDC: Operational Review Task Force - Key Documents, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - JDC: Operational Review Task Force, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - JDC: Operational Review Task Force, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - JDC: Co-Chair, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - JDC: Project, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Moving Forward Staff Meeting: Omni Hotel, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - MS Termination Letter, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - MS/Digitization Plan, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - MS Contract, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Microsoft Master Agreement, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Microsoft Non-Disclosure Agreement, 2007-2009 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Mellon Foundation: Taiga Forum, 2006-2007 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Mass Digitization, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Marcive Enhanced GPO Database, 1998-2011 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Map Collection, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Future of Maps Collections, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Near East Collection, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - MSSA Scholarly Resources, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Architectural Archives (MSSA), 2006 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - MSSA Grant Proposals, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Special Collections:Szary, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Archives and MSS: Szary: Manuscripts and Archives memos with Catalog Department, 2002-2004 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - MSSA and SAMMA System, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - MSSA: E-Records: Electronic Records, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - MSSA-Gehry/Lewis, 2003-2005 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Shoah/A-V, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Yale History Online, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Tech Services Accessions (MSSA), 2009 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - MSSA: Preservation Papers, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Medical Library Publications, 1993-2005 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Medical Library Documents, 2002-2004 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Library Technology Research and Planning, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Luna Imaging (INSIGHT): License Addendum, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Office of Digital Assets and Infrastructure, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Kirtas Digitizing Project, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - MacMillan Center: African (Swahili) Dictionary, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Proposal Catalog African Language Material, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Reorganization, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Technical Services Reorganization: Pt.1, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Technical Services Reorganization: Pt.2, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Rush Books/Flags, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Ross Archive of African Art, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Scholars as Librarians Program, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Reorganization Material, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Sterling Memorial Library Floor Plans, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Economic Growth Center Digital Library: August 2003 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Economic Growth Center Digital Library: February 2004: Pt.1 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Economic Growth Center Digital Library: February 2004: Pt.2 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Economic Growth Center Digital Library: Phase 2, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Business Case for Change: Acquiring Materials for Sterling Memorial Library, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Strategic Planning, 2006-2007 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Library Management Council: Strike Contingency Discussion, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Ex Libris to ProQuest Affects Yale Staff and Patrons, 2014 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Supervisory Assessment, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Supervisory Effectiveness, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Next Generation Public Catalog: Library Usability and Assessment, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Library ODAI, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - ODAI Steering Policy and Shared Practice, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Online Access to Research in the+A51:C87 Environment United Nations- Research Project+DA51:A73, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Office of Digital Assets and Infrastructure Metadata, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Online Computer Library Center Registry of Copyright Evidence Pilot, 2004-2008 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Online Public Access Catalog Next Generation, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Orbis Failover/Disaster Recovery Report, 39630 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Orbis Hardware Refresh, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Orbis, Research Libraries Information Network, 1985-1999 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Process Improvement, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Acquisition Process Improvement, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Process Improvement, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Process Improvement, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Process Improvement, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Reengineering Technical Services, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Reengineering Reevaluation, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - ProQuest Digital Archiving Access Program from University Microfilms International Dissertation Publishing, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Rescue Repository, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Technical Services Management Group/ Review Plaza, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Technical Services Annual Report Acquisitions: Annual Reports, 2006-2012 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Training Issues Meeting May, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Shared Server Discussion, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Acquisitions Goals Catalog Metadata Services Integrated Systems, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Library System Office Organization, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Web Workstation- Karen Reardon, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Orbis 2 Final Report, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Budget, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Library System Office Retreat, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - MetaLib Planning, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Rescue Repository, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Special Effects/ Ex Libris Amendment to License 20Mar2006 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Vital/Vines Contract, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Vital Contract, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Vital Implementation, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Visionary Technology in Library Solutions - Vital- Vines, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Visionary Technology in Library Solutions - Vital Final Report, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Vital Contract, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Vital Trial, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Vital/ Visionary Technology in Library Solutions, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Vital Digital Asset Software, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Visionary Technology in Library Solutions - Vital - Fedora, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Visionary Technology in Library Solutions Contract, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Visual Resource Collection Agreement, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Withdrawal Policy, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - User Assessment Usability Program, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Unlocking Collections 18 Jan 08, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Yale's Unlocking Collections Report, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Unlocking Collections, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Workflows- Yale, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - XmetL (Xmetal) Finding Aid Authority Tool, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Yale University Art Gallery Digital Collections, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Yale Art Gallery Data Warehouse Image System, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Visionary Technology in Library Solutions / Yale Daily News Digital Conversion, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Yale Daily News Letter of Agreement, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Yale Indian Papers Project Part 2, 2007, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Yale Indian Papers Project Part 1, 2007, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Yale Repository, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Retrospective Conversion of Official Card Catalog
    - OCLC Conversion Official, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - MSSA: Yale Publications, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Medical Library RECON, 1995-2001 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - LSF Miscellaneous (from MOC), 2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Lewis Walpole Library (RECON), 1998 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Harvard RECON, 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Government Documents (RECON), 1993-1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Geology RECON, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Divinity (OCLC sample records), 1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Divinity (RECON), 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Database Mgt./Catalog Mgt (Dept. History), 1987-1997 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - CCL RECON, 1992-1996 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Art RECON: Clean up, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Art (RECON) OCLC Sample Records, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Art (RECON), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Arts Project PR, 1991-1998 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - BRBL RECON, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - BRBL RECON (RLA), 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - BRBL RLA Quality Control, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - EAC RECON, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - CMT Training, 1997-1998 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Local Headings, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Location Codes, 1989-2000 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Official Cards Samples prop documentation: Pt.1, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Official Cards Samples prop documentation: Pt.2, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Analytics, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Official Catalog: OCLC Analysis, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Official Catalog: OCLC Operator Instructions, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Official Catalog-General and Historical, 1928-1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - OCLC Invoices: ART, DIV, LWL, 1997-1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - RECON: BHPP, 1994-1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - RCAC: Pt.1, 1997-2001 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - RCAC: Pt.2, 1995-1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - RECON Coordinating Committee, 1987-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - RECON: Latin Americana: Pt.1, 1990-1996 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - RECON: Latin Americana: Pt.2, 1989-1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - RECON: Numismatics: Pt.1, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)